## **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

- Email amitsargar@gmail.com
- Mobile (+91) 9595666995
- Total work experience
  9 Years 11 Months
- Social Link https://asargar.github.io

#### **KEY SKILLS**

Angular

Java Full Stack Developer

Java Spring Boot

Openshift

Jenkins

GIT

Helm

Splunk

## **OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS**

City Pune

Country INDIA

# LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

# **Amit Sargar**

**Assistant Vice President** 

## **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I am an Assistant Vice President at Deutsche Bank, with oveall 10 years of experience in full-stack development. I ensure successful end-to-end project delivery, leading high-impact projects that improve efficiency and productivity. Recognized as the go-to person for technical challenges. I excel in team settings, adapt well to change, and perform effectively under pressure, consistently solving problems and meeting productivity goals.

#### **EDUCATION**

2015

MCA

Veermata Jijabai Technical Institute (VJTI), Mumbai

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Mar 2020 -Present **Assistant Vice President** 

## Deutsche Bank, India

As a Full Stack Developer, I handle development from Angular to Spring Boot and manage deployment as well.

Notably, I developed a generic, configuration-based dashboard adaptable for similar views with minimal effort.

Additionally, I have been involved in migration projects from OCP3 to OCP4 and disaster recovery strategy of applications.

Dec 2016 - Mar 2020 Consultant

## **Deloitte Consulting USI**

Worked on the Agent Portal and upgraded the payment gateway for PCI compliance using Authorize.js. Represented Deloitte in the **Code Gladiator Finals** (2017, 2018), earning top recognition and participating in a Guinness World Record event.

Jan 2015 - Dec 2016

Associate Software Engineer

## Pragmatix Services Pvt. Lmt.

**Started as an intern**, I developed multiple platform modules, including a Smart Search module and a Download Automation solution for bulk file downloads, and enhanced the reporting framework.

After a 6-month internship, I contributed to the design, development, and optimization of the Rule Engine for NPA and EWS solutions and the Reporting Dashboard.